bluekangaroo.com 2013-09-17

# Blue Kangaroo - Privacy Policy

Last modified: August 24, 2012

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by ChoozOn Corporation, including services and websites under the Blue Kangaroo brand. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website at [privacy@BlueKangaroo.com](mailto:privacy@BlueKangaroo.com)[](mailto:privacy@choozon.com). 

### Blue Kangaroo is about your Choices

When you sign up for an Account, we ask you for personal information. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from our services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information. You can access the Settings page to review and edit the information associated with your Account.

### Accessing and Updating Personal Information

We make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Because of the way we maintain certain services, after you delete your information, residual copies may take a period of time before they are deleted from our active servers and may remain in our backup systems. 

ChoozOn regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy. When we receive formal written complaints, it is ChoozOn's policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between ChoozOn and an individual. 

### Choices

You can use our service to review and control the information stored in your Account. When you register for the Blue Kangaroo Service, you may provide your name, email address, location (ZIP code), and gender as information stored in your Account. When you use the Blue Kangaroo Service, you may designate specific brands as your personal preferences stored in your Account by (i) clicking on a “Follow” button for the deal board of a particular brand, or (i) initiating the forwarding of a brand’s marketing emails to your Blue Kangaroo Account instead of to your personal email account. You can initiate the forwarding of marketing emails either by directing a specific brand to deliver its marketing emails to your ChoozOn or Blue Kangaroo email address and/or by directing Blue Kangaroo to sweep your personal email inbox for marketing emails from all recognized brands and redirect those emails to your Blue Kangaroo Account. 

By clicking on a “Follow” button to designate a specific brand as your personal preference or by initiating the forwarding of their marketing emails to your Blue Kangaroo Account, you are giving permission to ChoozOn and to any brand you designate to make use of what the brand and/or ChoozOn may know about your personal preferences to recommend relevant offers. Blue Kangaroo will monitor the brand's offers around the clock, consider which offers match your interests, and whether you qualify for them, and post the most relevant offers into your Inbox. Blue Kangaroo may also consider your activities in using the service - for example, the products that you may search for - to further refine our recommendations of personalized offers. The brand may apply what it and/or ChoozOn may know about your interests and information stored in your Account to send you relevant messages and offers. A brand may do this on the Blue Kangaroo website or any other digital media channel. You may withdraw your permission for this by "un-following" any brand at any time.

### Information sharing

ChoozOn shares personal information only with other companies or individuals outside of ChoozOn in the following limited circumstances: 

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information. 
  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of ChoozOn, its users or the public as required or permitted by law. 

If ChoozOn becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

### Information we collect and how we use it

We may collect the following types of information in addition to the information you provide: 

**Cookies -** Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some of our features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. When you visit the Blue Kangaroo website, we send one or more cookies to your computer or other device. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, improving offer selection, ad selection, and tracking user responses. ChoozOn also uses cookies in its advertising services to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads across the web and on Blue Kangaroo services. 

**Log information** \- When you access Blue Kangaroo services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, your interaction with a service, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account. 

**User communications** \- When you send email or other communications to ChoozOn and/or Blue Kangaroo, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. When you send and receive SMS messages to or from one of our services that provides SMS functionality, we may collect and maintain information associated with those messages, such as the phone number, the wireless carrier associated with the phone number, the content of the message, and the date and time of the transaction. We may use your email address to communicate with you about our services. 

**Affiliated Blue Kangaroo Services on other sites** \- We offer some of our services on or through other web sites, browser extensions, toolbars, mobile network platforms and other software applications owned or managed by our business partners. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to ChoozOn in order to deliver the service. We process such information under this Privacy Policy. 

**Third Party Applications** \- ChoozOn may make available third party applications through its services. The information collected by ChoozOn when you enable a third party application is processed under this Privacy Policy. Information collected by the third party application provider is governed by its privacy policies. ChoozOn works with various affiliate networks (such as Commission Junction, LinkShare, and Google Affiliate Network) which may place and use cookies to help marketers, advertisers and publishers, including ChoozOn, serve and manage offers and ads across the web. You may choose to opt out of their cookies at any time by using their respective affiliate network's opt-out process.

**Other sites** \- This Privacy Policy applies to Blue Kangaroo and/or ChoozOn services only. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results, sites that include ChoozOn and/or Blue Kangaroo applications, products or services, or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. 

In addition to the above, we may use the information we collect to: 

  * Provide, maintain, protect, and improve our services (including advertising services) and develop new services; and 
  * Protect the rights or property of ChoozOn or our users. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. 

ChoozOn processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America and in other countries, including Jordan. In some cases, we process personal information outside your own country. 

### Information security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

We restrict access to personal information to ChoozOn employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.
